[Music]
do you guys go to the gym I go to the
gym but you already knew that but I
don't think I'll ever be as buff as this
kangaroo look at
that oh my
God he's like an
alien holy [ __ ] like he is jacked like
has he been stacking do you even lift
bro yes I'm intimidating I feel like
he's about to kick my ass like like yo
bro I'll rip your head off and stuff it
in my pouch like a trophy [ __ ]
now the version you guys sent me only
has 12,000 views so unless there's
another copy out there I think fairly
fresh look at that oh my God and I don't
blame the cameraman for laughing his ass
off me how do you even get this buff
yeah I've been bench pressing koala
bears all day you know I typically eat
plants and berries but no trans fat you
know can you spot me you know it even
seems like he's looking for an excuse to
flex like yep you should check out the
other exhibits over
there so this next video is great it's
really squirrel so this is someone's pet
squirrel trying to bury a nut in a dog
spur a I have nothing to say about this
other than it's [ __ ] cute and like it
is cute but he makes a serious attempt
to cover up that nut no no one will
think to look here so I found this over
on a Blog I read sometimes called io9
and it has 4 million views damn so it's
blowing up and why do they have a pet
squirrel and like why isn't that dog
murdering that squirrel look I'm not
saying the dog should murder the
squirrel it's just all right I have four
cats and when they see a squirrel
they're
like and if you look at the dog the dog
just couldn't be more apathetic I mean
he just doesn't care he's like you know
all those [ __ ] I have to give I buried
them in the backyard and if you're
curious how the video ends it looks like
the squirrel and up hiding his nuts in
the laundry basket now high-s speed
chases will never not be exciting but
this is the first time I've ever seen
one where the cop was actually wearing a
camera [ __ ] now this cop's
actually not a traditional cop he's
apparently part of the Arkansas Game and
Fish Commission so if you're thinking
about fishing without a permit he will
[ __ ] you up now the video gets
unfortunately funny when the officer
catches the suspect who appears to be a
total
methhead
[ __ ] now this whole scene apparently
went down back in August of 2012 and
it's just now blowing up either that or
it's an elaborate commercial for Google
Glass see to me this is like the real
life Breaking Bad people fantasize about
living this Breaking Bad life life but
in reality that's what the real Jesse
Pinkman would look like now there's a
lot of contention about how the officer
handled the arrest after the suspect got
out of the car but you know if you're on
met driving on the wrong side of the
highway endangering lives I'd say
getting cursed at with a gun stuck to
your neck it's a possibility you know I
got of feel bad for the guy but it's
like that with 80% of the videos that
you send me it's like I feel bad for the
person but at the same time I'm like
dude what the [ __ ] were you thinking see
and now this guy he's busted he's going
to go to jail this will probably be his
cellmate do you even [ __ ] bro and you
know what else after seeing this video
I'm seriously having second thoughts
about ever doing meth but that's all my
time guys I'll see you later in the week
uh don't forget to check out the full
videos links are down below in the
description I'm Ray William Johnson and
I approve this
message yeah I've been bench pressing
koala bears all day you know I typically
eat plants and berries but no trans fats
you know can you spot me can you give me
a spot you a spot can you get a spot Can
you spot over there you spot spot you
spot me to spot you spot him I'll spot
you sp is spot on my wall dog name spot
somebody not know how to flush the
toilet after they've had a
[Music]
[ __ ] oh it's you hey